Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory9 Mss.B.B61.inventory09
American Philosophical Society
Franz Boas Papers: Inventory (M)
1862-1942
Mss.B.B61.inventory09
American Philosophical Society
1.0 section
This is part of the large inventory for the Franz Boas Papers (Mss B B61). For complete information concerning this collection, please view the Collection Description.
Boas, Franz, 1858-1942
Scope and Contents note
Due to the size of the collection, the content for Series I has been divided into multiple inventories. Please follow the links below to browse the inventories.
Inventories
Correspondents A
Correspondents B
Correspondents C
Correspondents D
Correspondents E-G
Correspondents H
Correspondents I-K
Correspondents L
Correspondents M
Correspondents N-Q
Correspondents R
Correspondents S
Correspondents T-V
Correspondents W-Z
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents M
  - M----, M.(Pres.'s Office, Rockefeller F.) (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 13; 1p.
  - M., W.H. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 23; postcard
  - Maass, F. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 13; 1p.
  - Maass, H.H. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 29; 1p.
  - Mabbott, T.O. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1925 May 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 12; 2p.
  - Mabie & Maidmont (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 6
  - McAfee, M., 1937 Sept. 3 (Box 58)
    Scope and Contents note
    (to Boas)
  - MacAlbert, Cora (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 29; 1p.
  - Macallum, A.B. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 3; 2p.
  - McAneny, George (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 June 2
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 12; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 2; 8p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 29
    - From Boas, 1914 May 28; 10p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 7
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 21
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 May 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 May 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 May 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 May 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 June 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 June 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 June 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 June 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - See Schwab, G.H., May 26, 1906
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1909 June 11
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 5
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 May 31; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 2; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 27; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 27; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1918 May 28; 1p.
    - (Enc: Abraham Flexner to George McAneny, May 24, 1918., 1928 June 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - (Enc: Memorial of Carl Schurz.), 1929 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p.
    - G. McAneny -- from J. Bertram, 1918 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - G. McAneny -- from N.L. Britton, 1918 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - G. McAneny -- from A. Flexner, 1918 May 24; 1p.
    - G. McAneny -- from C.A. Oberwager, 1928 Dec. 21
  - McAneny, Mrs. George (Marjorie) (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 July 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 July 1; 1p.
    - M. McAneny -- to Braun, 1919 Dec. 6; 2p.
  - McAnney, B.O. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 26; 1p.
  - Macari, Leopold (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas
      - Enc. with McFarland, R.A., Feb. 4, 1935; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 20; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1938 July 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 July 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 July 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 9; 3p.
    - See Boas, F. (open Letter) Nov. 25, 1940., 1940 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 14; 15p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Sept. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 2; 1p.
  - McAvoy, Clifford T. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 24; 1p.
      (Enc: Council for Pan American Democracy Memorandum on Luiz Carlos Prestes)
    - C.T. McAvoy -- from N.M. Butler, 1938 Jan. 7
    - (Enc. with McAvoy, C.T. to Efron, D., Jan. 31, 1938)
    - C.T. McAvoy -- from Michele Cantarella, 1938 Jan. 28
    - C.T. McAboy -- to D. Efron, 1938 Jan. 31; 3p.
    - (Enc: Moody, P.D. Butler, N.M. McCracken, H.N., Jan. 5, 1938 Jan. 7, 1938 Jan. 13, 1938)
    - C.T. McAvoy -- from H.N. McCracken, 1938 Jan. 13
    - (Enc. with McAvoy, C.T. to Efron, D., Jan. 31, 1938)
    - C.T. McAvoy -- from Paul D. Moody, 1938 Jan. 5
    - (Enc. with McAvoy to Efron, Jan. 31, 1938)
  - McBain, H.L. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 15; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 16; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 June 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 3; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 12; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 June 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 6; 1p.
    - H.L. McBain -- to Council for research in the social sciences, 1934 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - H.L. McBain -- from E.E. Day, 1934 Feb. 10
  - McBride, J.K. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1910 May 16
  - McCallum, R. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 19; 1p.
  - McCastline, W.H. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 20; 2p.
  - McCastline, Mrs. W.H. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 6; 1p.
  - McChesney, C.E. (Box 58)
    - To Fachtenberg, 1913 June 6
  - McClean, L.D. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - (See Boas, F. to Tyler, J.M., Nov. 13, 1919)
  - McClintock, Charles T. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1896 Oct. 14
  - McCloy, C.H. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1919 July 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 July 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 16; 1p.
  - A.C. McClung & Co. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 18
  - McClure, B. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 24; 2p.
    - B. McClure -- from W.K. Moorehead, 1935 Oct. 14
    - (Enc. with Moorehead, W.K., Oct. 15, 1935)
  - McConn, C.M. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 22; 3p.
  - McConnell, Donald (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 1; 1p.
      (Enc: Aims of the Conference on Pan-American democracy)
    - See Soule, George, 1938 Dec. 11
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 4; 1p.
  - McConnell, Francis J. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 5; teleg.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 25; teleg.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 30; teleg.
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 2; 1p.
  - McConnell, H. Ormonde (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 6p.
      - (Enc. with McConnell, H.O. to Haiti. Sec. de Etat..., Nov. 30, 1940)
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 8; 2p.
    - (Enc: Volel, Edvard to McConnell, H.O. Feb. 1, 1941., 1941 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - (Enc: Papers re Teaching of Creole in Haiti.), 1941 Feb. 28; 1p.
      (Enc: Clipping)
    - H.O. McConnell -- to Haiti. Sec. d'Etat..., 1940 Nov. 30; 1p.
      (Enc: Rapport sur notre méthode pour l'enseignement de la lecture du créole aux paysans)
    - H.O. McConnell -- from Edvard Volel, 1941 Feb. 1
    - (Enc. with McConnell, H.O., Feb. 8, 1941)
  - McConnell, Luther G. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1940 June 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 June 20; 2p.
  - McCorison, J.L., Jr. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1942 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 20; 1p.
  - McCormick, F. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 8
  - McCormick, James (Box 58)
    - J. McCormick -- from J.W. McGuire, 1924 Feb. 24
  - MacCracken, H.N. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept.8; 1p.
    - H.N. MacCracken -- to C.T. McAvoy, 1938 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - (Enc. with McAvoy to Efron, Jan. 31, 1938)
  - McCrea, Nelson G. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 23; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 1; 1p.
  - McCrea, R.C. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 May 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 22; 1p.
  - McCurdy, A. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 9; 1p.
  - MacCurdy, George G. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 28
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 6
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 21
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 29
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 3
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 25
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 22; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1916 May 22
    - (See Boas, F. to Gordon, G.B. May 22, 1916, 1916 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 8
    - (See Boas, F. to Dixon, R.B. Dec. 8, 1916, 1917 Jan. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 June 8
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1912 Sept. 27
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 26
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1917 June 7
    - To Boas, 1917 June 12
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - (Enc: American school of prehistoric research. Notice of 10th summer term), 1931 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - (Enc: International congress of linguistics. 2, Geneva, 1931. Program), 1932 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - G.G. MacCurdy -- to F. Frassetto, 1919 Mar. 8; 1p.
  - McCurdy, Henry B. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 28; 1p.
  - McDavid, R.I., Jr. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 June 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 8; 1p.
  - MacDonald, Arthur (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1893 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 7; 1p.
  - McDonald, D.A. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 13; teleg.
    - D.A. McDonald -- from G.A. Reichard telegram, n.d.
  - Macdonald, Dwight (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 6; 1p.
  - McDonald, James G. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 22; 1p.
  - McDonald, R.A. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 18; 1p.
  - McDonald, William (MacDonald) J. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1918 Aug. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1890 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1890 July 3
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 13; 1p.
  - MacDougal, D.T. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 23; 2p.
  - McDougall, M.M. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1890 Sept. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1890 Sept. 14; 2p.
  - MacDougall, R. (Box 58)
    - See Hovey, E.O. (margin), Oct. 8, 1907
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 8
    - R. MacDougall -- from E.O. Hovey, 1907 Oct. 8
  - MacDowell, Edward A. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 13; 1p.
  - McFaddin, G. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1893 Dec. 25; 2p.
  - McFarland, A.C. (Box 58)
    - A.C. McFarland -- to J.M.P. Smith, 1920 Aug. 23; 1p.
  - McFarland, Ross A. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 4; 2p.
      (Enc: Macari, L.M. report
      McFarland, R.A. Cultural conflict and adjustment in a selected group of Italians 4p.
      Changes in attitudes relative to the Folkways and mores of a specific Italian group with change in environment. 10p.
      Questionnaire on the Changes... 15p.
      Family schedule 7p.)
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 17; 3p.
      - (Enc. with Columbia Univ. Council for research in the social sciences., Oct. 13, 1936.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - R.A. McFarland -- to P.M. Hayden, 1934 May 14; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Hayden, P.M. to Columbia Univ. Council for research in the social sciences, May 15, 1934)
    - Anna Bogue -- to R.A.Md, 1934 June 29; 1p.
  - MacFarlane, Helen G. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 13; 1p.
  - McGee, Anita Newcomb (Box 59)
    - From Boas, 1905 June 14
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Mar. 15; 4p
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 28,June 7,July 4
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 14
  - McGee, Louis J. (Box 59)
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 27; 1p
  - McGee, W.J. (Box 59)
    - From Boas, 1893 Dec. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1895 June 27
    - From Boas, 1895 July 29
    - From Boas, 1895 Aug. 23
    - From Boas, 1897 Jan. 1; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1898 May 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 May 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Nov. 15; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Nov. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Nov. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 May 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 May 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 June 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 June 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 June 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Aug. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Sept. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Feb. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Oct. 6
    - From Boas, 1900 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Apr. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Apr. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 May 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 May 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1901 May 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1901 May 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 May 20
    - From Boas, 1901 June 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1901 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Jan. 25; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Feb. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 26; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Mar. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Apr. 21
    - From Boas, 1902 May 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 May 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 May 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 May 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 June 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 June 12
    - From Boas, 1902 June 18; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1902 June 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Aug. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Sept.4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1902 Sept.4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1903 May 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Sept. 15; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1905 June 14
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 May 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Sept. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Sept. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 4; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 31; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 May 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 May 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1894 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1894 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1894 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1894 May 16
    - To Boas, 1894 June 11
    - To Boas, 1894 July 24
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 6
    - To Boas, 1894 Sept. 1
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1895 June 14
    - To Boas, 1895 July 6
    - To Boas, 1895 July 8
    - To Boas, 1895 Aug. 19
    - To Boas, 1895 Aug. 21
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1896 May 6
    - To Boas, 1896 May 15
    - To Boas, 1896 June 23
    - To Boas, 1896 June 23
    - To Boas, 1896 July 14
    - To Boas, 1896 Aug. 5
    - To Boas, 1896 Sept. 11
    - To Boas, 1896 Sept. 15
    - To Boas, 1896 Sept. 21
    - To Boas, 1896 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1896 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1896 Dec. 5